A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - Real Estate, 1977-1981; 23
    - Estate Fountain River - Sale (Box 392, Folder 2)
    - Estate Fountain River - Sale - Printed Material (Box 392, Folder 3)
    - Estate Fountain River - Sale - Sotheby Parke Bernet International Realty Corp. (Box 392, Folder 4)
    - Estate Fountain River - Slides (Box 393, Folder 1)
    - Fairington (Box 393, Folder 2-3, Box 394, Folder 1)
    - Fairington - Meadowood Apts. - Freeze Damage (Box 394, Folder 2)
    - Fairington - Meadowood Apts. - Sale (Box 394, Folder 3)
    - Hills Realty (Box 394, Folder 4)
    - Hills Realty - Parke-Bernet Galleries (Box 394, Folder 5)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 395, Folder 1-2)
      Restricted - Open in 2042.
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Accounting Manual (Box 395, Folder 3)
      Restricted - Open in 2042
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Finances (Box 395, Folder 4, Box 396, Folder 1-3, Box 397, Folder 1)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Maps (Box 397, Folder 2)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Memos (Box 397, Folder 3)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Minutes-Meetings (Box 397, Folder 4)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Rental Houses (Box 397, Folder 5)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Pocantico Hills - Playhouse (Box 398, Folder 1)
    - Interstate North Associates (Box 398, Folder 2-3, Box 399, Folder 1-3, Box 400, Folder 1)
    - Cousins Properties, Inc. (CPI) (Box 400, Folder 2)
    - Olohana Corporation - Maps (Box 400, Folder 3)
    - L'Enfant Plaza (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - L'Enfant Plaza - Finances (Box 401, Folder 2)
    - L'Enfant Plaza - Legal (Box 401, Folder 3)
    - L'Enfant Plaza - Minutes-Meetings, 1977-1978 (Box 401, Folder 4)
    - L'Enfant Plaza - Superannuation Schemes of the Electricity Council, U.K. (Box 402, Folder 1)
    - L'Enfant Plaza - Marrriot Hotel (Box 402, Folder 2)
    - Mauna Lani Resort (Box 402, Folder 3)
    - Olohana Corporation - Corporate Structure (Box 402, Folder 4)
    - Olohana Corporation - A-Z (Box 402, Folder 5-6)
    - Olohana Corporation - Beach Access Lawsuit (Box 403, Folder 1-3, Box 404, Folder 1-2)
    - Olohana Corporation - Cowell and Company (Box 403, Folder 4, Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Olohana Corporation - Finances (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Olohana Corporation - Golf Courses (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Olohana Corporation - Highways-Roads (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Olohana Corporation - Mauna Kea Fairways and Association (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Olohana Corporation - Mauna Kea Fairways and Association - Minutes-Meetings (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Olohana Corporation - Mauna Kea Land Corp. (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Olohana Corporation - The Newport Development Co. (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Olohana Corporation - Ouli Development (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Olohana Corporation - Mrs. Lyman Perry-Fiske (Anna L.) (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Olohana Corporation - Planning-Review (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Olohana Corporation - Progress Charts (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Olohana Corporation - Projects (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Olohana Corporation - Smart, Richard - Leasehold (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Olohana Corporation - UAL Inc. (Box 407, Folder 4, Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Olohana Corporation - Water (Box 408, Folder 2-3)
    - Panola Associates - Dekalb Investing-Fairington Associates (re liquidation) (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico Hills - A-Z (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills - Future (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark - Brochure, 1980 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark - Brochure, 1977 (Box 409, Folder 5-6, Box 410, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark - Sleepy Hollow Restoration (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark - Printed Material (Box 410, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - C.W. Frye - Pocantico Development-Frank Cross (Box 411, Folder 1)
      Restricted - Open in 2029
    - Pocantico Hills - Future - Frye, Clayton W. (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills - Land Use Study - Sasaki, 1981 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1977-1981 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Historic Landmark, 1977-1981 (Box 412, Folder 1-2)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Pocantico Recommendations (Box 412, Folder 3-4, Box 413, Folder 1-2)
    - Pocantico Hills - Housing Plans, 1981 (Box 413, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Park Service (Box 413, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Park Service - A-Z (Box 413, Folder 5)
    - Pocantico Hills - Pocantico Committee (Box 414, Folder 1)
    - Pocantico Hills - Property (Box 414, Folder 2)
    - Pocantico Hills - Property - Buttermilk Hill (Box 414, Folder 3)
    - Pocantico Hills - National Trust for Historic Preservation - Agreements (Box 414, Folder 4)
    - Pocantico Hills - Public Affairs (Box 415, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center - Guidelines of Business (Box 415, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Center - A-K (Box 415, Folder 3-5)
    - Rockefeller Center - M-Z (Box 416, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller Center - Cushman and Wakefield, Inc. (Box 416, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances (Box 418, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Finances-Investments (Box 418, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Minutes-Meetings (Box 419, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller Center - Miscellaneous Meetings (Box 419, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center - Printed Material (Box 420, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center - RCTV (Box 420, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio City Music Hall - A-Z (Box 420, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio City Music Hall - Printed Material (Box 420, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Radio City Music Hall Productions Inc. (Box 417, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Real Estate Development Committee (Box 421, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Celanese (Box 421, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Flower, Inc. (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Morris (Box 421, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Time (Box 421, Folder 5, Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rock-Uris (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Brothers - Leases (Box 417, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Center Construction Corp. (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Center Development Corp. - A-Z (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller Center, Inc. - Rockefeller Center Management Corp. (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Rockresorts - A-Z (Box 423, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockresorts - Finances (Box 423, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Cerromar Beach Hotel (Box 423, Folder 5)
    - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach (Box 424, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Kapalua Bay Hotel (Box 424, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockresorts - Kapalua Bay Hotel - Printed Material (Box 424, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Halekulani Hotel (Box 424, Folder 5)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - General (Box 425, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - A-Z (Box 425, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Finances (Box 425, Folder 4, Box 426, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Printed Matter (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - Little Dix Bay - Virgin Gorda Marina (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea (Box 426, Folder 5)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - A-C (Box 426, Folder 6)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - D-Z (Box 427, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Blueprints and Maps (Box 427, Folder 3-4, Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea - Chapel (Box 428, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Finances (Box 428, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Sale - A-Z (Box 428, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Sale (Box 429, Folder 1-2, Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Fairways (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Memos (Box 431, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Minutes-Meetings (Box 417, Folder 3, Box 430, Folder 2-4)
    - Rockresorts - Suicide Six (Box 431, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - Printed Matter (Box 431, Folder 5)
    - Rockresorts - Mt. Tom and Suicide Six (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Victoria International Corp. (Box 432, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockresorts - Victoria International Corp. - Reports (Box 432, Folder 4, Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Seal Harbor (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Seal Harbor - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Gardens (Box 433, Folder 3)
    - UAL Inc. (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Offers - A-F (Box 433, Folder 4)
    - Offers - G-N (Box 434, Folder 1-3)
    - Offers - O-Z (Box 435, Folder 1-3)
    - Offers - Yerba Buena Center (Box 435, Folder 4)
  - Religion, 1977-1981; 24
    - Religion - A-E (Box 436, Folder 1-6)
    - Religion - F-N (Box 437, Folder 1-5)
    - Religion - O-Z (Box 438, Folder 1-4)
    - Riverdale Center of Religious Research (Box 439, Folder 1)
    - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks (Box 439, Folder 2)
    - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks - Printed Matter (Box 439, Folder 3)
    - Agape (Box 439, Folder 4)
    - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 439, Folder 5)
    - American Friends Service Committee (Box 440, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'raith (Box 440, Folder 2)
    - Christian Science Association (Box 440, Folder 3)
    - Council on Religion and International Affairs (Box 440, Folder 4)
    - The Genesis Project (Box 441, Folder 1-2)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 441, Folder 3)
    - Seamen's Church Institute (Box 441, Folder 4)
    - United Church of Christ (Box 441, Folder 5)
    - Zen Studies Society (Box 441, Folder 6, Box 442, Folder 1)
    - Zen Center, Rochester, NY (Box 442, Folder 2)
    - Churches - A-Ch (Box 442, Folder 3-6)
    - Churches - Ci-S (Box 443, Folder 1-5)
    - Churches - S-Z (Box 444, Folder 1-3)
    - Churches - Brick Presbyterian Church (Box 444, Folder 4)
    - Churches - Cathedral Church of St. John the Divine (Box 444, Folder 5)
    - Churches - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. (Box 444, Folder 6)
    - Churches - National Council of Churches of Christ in the U.S. - Division of Church & Society (Box 445, Folder 1)
    - Churches - Riverside Church (Box 445, Folder 2)
    - Churches - Riverside Church - Contributions (Box 445, Folder 3)
    - Churches - St. John's Episcopal Church (Box 445, Folder 4)
    - Churches - Union Church of Pocantico Hills (Box 445, Folder 5, Box 446, Folder 1)
    - Missions - A-Z (Box 446, Folder 2)
    - Missions - New York City Mission Society (Box 446, Folder 3-4, Box 447, Folder 1)
    - Missions - New York City Mission Society - Printed Material (Box 447, Folder 2)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation (Box 447, Folder 3)
    - Missions - Quebec-Labrador Foundation - Printed Material (Box 447, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1962-1981 (Bulk: 1977-1981); 1977-1981; 25
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. (Box 447, Folder 5)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - A-Z (Box 448, Folder 1-2)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Gulfstream II Exchange Agreement (Box 448, Folder 3)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Flight Book (Box 448, Folder 4)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Board of Directors - Minutes/Meetings (Box 448, Folder 5)
    - Airplanes - Wayfarer Ketch Corp. - Printed Material (Box 448, Folder 6)
    - Awards (Box 449, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Brothers - General Correspondence and Meetings (Box 449, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Brothers - Meetings (Box 449, Folder 3-5)
    - Rockefeller Family (Box 450, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller Family Cousins (Box 450, Folder 2)
    - Fifth Generation (Box 450, Folder 3)
    - Trusts (Box 450, Folder 4)
    - Aldrich, Hope (Box 450, Folder 5)
    - Aldrich, Hope - Charitable Lead Trusts (Box 450, Folder 6)
    - Aldrich, Hope - Grants - A-Z (Box 450, Folder 7)
    - Aldrich, Hope - Giving Program (Box 450, Folder 8)
    - Bartley, Bruce (Box 451, Folder 1)
    - Chasin, Richard M. (Mrs.) (Laura S. Rockefeller) (Box 451, Folder 2-3)
    - Chasin, Dana James (Box 451, Folder 4)
      Biographical / Historical
    - Chasin, Alexandra (Box 451, Folder 5)
    - Case, Peter Rockefeller (Box 451, Folder 6)
    - Dayton, Eric John (Box 451, Folder 7)
    - Dayton, Eric John - Charitable Lead Trust - A-Z (Box 451, Folder 9-12, Box 452, Folder 1)
    - Dayton, Mark Brandt (Mrs.) (Alida Davison Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 2)
    - Dayton - Giving Program (Box 452, Folder 3)
    - Dayton - Loans - Ms. Foundation for Education and Communications, Inc. (Box 452, Folder 4)
    - Dulany-Quattrone (Box 452, Folder 5)
    - Kaiser, Walter, J. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Neva G. Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 6)
    - Growald, Paul Jeffrey (Mr. and Mrs.) (Eileen McGrath Rockefeller) (Box 452, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, Eileen (Box 452, Folder 8)
    - Lindstrom, Christopher Rockefeller (Box 453, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Estate (Box 453, Folder 3-5)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust (Box 454, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - J. Richardson Dilworth (Box 454, Folder 2)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Trusts (Box 454, Folder 3)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust - Grants (Box 455, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Abby Rockefeller Mauze Charitable Trust - Grants - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 2-3)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - A-Z (Box 455, Folder 4)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Board of Directors (Box 455, Folder 5)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Contributions (Box 456, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Greenacre Park - Finances (Box 456, Folder 2-3)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Park - Insurance (Box 454, Folder 4)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Park - Legal (Box 454, Folder 5)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Park - Taxes (Box 454, Folder 6)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 456, Folder 4, Box 457, Folder 1-4)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Park Council (Box 457, Folder 5)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) - Greenacre Foundation - Requests (Box 460, Folder 1)
    - Mauze, Jean (Mrs.) (Abby Rockefeller) (Box 453, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas B. Morgan (Box 458, Folder 1)
    - Murphy, Carol (Box 458, Folder 2)
    - Murphy, James B II (Box 458, Folder 3)
    - Murphy, Malinda (Box 458, Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Malinda - Debut (Box 458, Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Margaretta H. (Wendy) (Box 458, Folder 6)
    - O'Neill, Abby (Gail) (Box 458, Folder 7)
    - O'Neill, Catherine, M. (Box 458, Folder 8)
    - O'Neill, David M. (Box 458, Folder 9)
    - O'Neill, Eliza Milton (Box 458, Folder 10)
    - O'Neill, George D. (Mr. and Mrs.) (Abby Milton) (Box 459, Folder 1)
    - O'Neill, George, Jr. (Box 459, Folder 2)
    - O'Neill, George, Jr. - Investments (Box 459, Folder 3)
    - O'Neill, Mr. and Mrs. Grover III (Laura K. Simpson) (Box 459, Folder 4)
    - O'Neill, Peter Meriwether (Box 459, Folder 5)
    - O'Neill, Wendy H. (Box 459, Folder 6)
    - Pierson, Claire M. (Box 459, Folder 7)
    - Pierson, Joseph (Box 459, Folder 8)
    - Pierson, Mary Louise (Box 459, Folder 9)
    - Pierson, Rachel (Box 459, Folder 10)
    - Rasmussen, Anne Marie (Box 459, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Ann R. (Ann Rockefeller) (Box 459, Folder 12)
    - Roberts, Ann R. (Ann Rockefeller) - Giving Program (Box 459, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller Abby A. (Box 459, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller, Abby A. - Investments (Clivus Multrum) (Box 458, Folder 11)
    - Rockefeller, David - A-E (Box 460, Folder 2-6)
    - Rockefeller, David - F-L (Box 461, Folder 1-5)
    - Rockefeller, David - M-S (Box 462, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - T-Z (Box 463, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - A-C (Box 463, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - D-R (Box 464, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - S-Z (Box 465, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 465, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 465, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - Japan-U.S. Businessmen's Conference (Box 465, Folder 6, Box 466, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Addresses-Remarks - Sample Speeches, 1979-1980 (Box 466, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - A-K (Box 466, Folder 4, Box 467, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - L-Z (Box 467, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Articles - Le Monde (Box 467, Folder 3-4, Box 468, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Autographs (Box 468, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Awards - A-Z (Box 468, Folder 3-4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Biographical Notes - William Wing (Box 468, Folder 5, Box 469, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Boats (Box 469, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Christmas gifts (Box 469, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Council of the Americas (Box 469, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners, Luncheons (Box 469, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Dinners, Luncheons - Overseas Development Council (Box 469, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Gifts (Box 470, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Giving Program (Box 470, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - International Advisory Committee (Box 470, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations to Speak - A-O (Box 470, Folder 4-7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations to Speak - P-Z (Box 471, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations to Speak - Miscellaneous (Box 471, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Invitations (Box 471, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Jury Duty (Box 471, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Legal (Box 471, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Legal - Milbank, Tweed, Hadley and McCloy (Box 474, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Photographs (Box 471, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David - Politics (Box 472, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property (Box 472, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Pocantico Hills (Box 474, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Seal Harbor (Box 472, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Property - Saint Barts (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David - Radio/TV (Box 472, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trips (Box 472, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, David - Trusts (Box 474, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David - Work of Arts (Box 472, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, David (Mrs.), Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box 473, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, David (Mrs.), Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Maine Coast Heritage Trust - Contributions (Box 473, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, David (Mrs.), Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - General Correspondence (Box 473, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, David (Mrs.), Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Pocantico Hills - Farm Project (Box 473, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, David (Mrs.), Margaret McGrath "Peggy" - Music Assistance Fund (Box 473, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, David, Jr. (Box 474, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Ingrid (Box 474, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, Jennifer (Box 474, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Sr (Box 473, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Sr. - The John D. Rockefeller Family Cemetery Corp. (Box 474, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Sr. (Mrs.), Laura Spelman (Box 473, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Box 473, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Mrs.), Abby A. (Box 473, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. (Mrs.), Martha Baird (Box 473, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - A-Z (Box 475, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Addresses - A-J (Box 475, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Addresses - K-Z (Box 476, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Addresses - Miscellaneous (Box 476, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - American Revolutionary Bicentennial (Box 476, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - American Revolutionary Bicentennial - National Committee for the Bicentennial Era (Box 476, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Articles - A-Z (Box 476, Folder 5-6)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Autographs (Box 477, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Biography (Box 477, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Contact Sheets (Box 477, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death (Box 477, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Clippings (Box 477, Folder 5-6)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - A-Be (Box 478, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - Bh-Ch (Box 479, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - Ch-D (Box 480, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - E-G (Box 481, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - H-J (Box 482, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - K-L (Box 483, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - M (Box 484, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - N-Pr (Box 485, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - Pr-R (Box 486, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - S (Box 487, Folder 1-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - T-W (Box 488, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - X-Z (Box 489, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Condolences - to Nelson A. Rockefeller (NAR) (Box 489, Folder 2-3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Memorial Service (Box 489, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Death - Memorial Service Booklet (Box 490, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd - Death - Mass Cards (Box 499, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd - Death - Memorial Books (Box 499, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd - Death - Tributes (Box 499, Folder 3-4, Box 500, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Dinners (Box 490, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Invitations to Speak (Box 490, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Photos (Box 490, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Memorials (Box 490, Folder 5)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Property (Box 490, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Radio-TV (Box 490, Folder 7)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Works of Art - American Art Collection (Box 490, Folder 8)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Purchases and Offers, 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Loans and Declinations, 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Works of Art - American Art Collection - Richardson, Dr. E. P., 1974-1978 (Box 491, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - Works of Art (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd - JDR 3rd Fund - A-F (Box 491, Folder 5)